let answers = [
  {
    question: "Closure is a function, that binds?",
    answers: ["Free variables", "Global variables"],
    correctAnswer: "Free variables",
  },
  {
    question: "Difference between let and var?",
    answers: ["Scope rules", "Block, function"],
    correctAnswer: "Block, function",
  },
  {
    question: "How map function works?",
    answers: ["Create array", "Apply function"],
    correctAnswer: "Create array",
  },
  {
    question: "Callback function use?",
    answers: ["Passed as argument", "Returns"],
    correctAnswer: "Passed as argument",
  },
  {
    question: "Document.ready in jQuery?",
    answers: ["DOM readiness", "Event listener"],
    correctAnswer: "DOM readiness",
  },

  {
    question: "What is the DOM?",
    answers: ["Document Object", "Model"],
    correctAnswer: "Document Object",
  },
  {
    question: "Significance of `this`?",
    answers: ["Function context", "Object"],
    correctAnswer: "Function context",
  },
  {
    question: "Difference: null vs undefined?",
    answers: ["Absence, assigned", "Object, primitive"],
    correctAnswer: "Absence, assigned",
  },
  {
    question: "`NaN` value meaning?",
    answers: ["Not a Number", "Null"],
    correctAnswer: "Not a Number",
  },
  {
    question: "Spread operator purpose?",
    answers: ["Shallow copy", "Concatenate"],
    correctAnswer: "Shallow copy",
  },
];
